hello YouTube world it is Friday and I
should be on video 25 but instead I'm on
video 23 I believe and but I'm gonna
catch up this weekend so sorry on Monday
help them on video musics today I'm
exhausted
I've spent the week with kindergarteners
not even really why do you say I was at
the mall all day which is horrible for
me but I had to get my car fixed and it
was the only thing nearby and yeah so
today my child is a kindergarten by
herself for the very first time and it
so now I get to clean my disaster of a
house but I still want to keep my
commitments of doing this video and well
as I will be writing for an hour I have
been sitting down in writing but it's
been disheartening upsetting that I just
I don't know how to convey what I want
to convey and it's just about sitting
down and doing it this is writing a
novel about an essay not a paragraph not
a tweet
so I'm not write a tweet like I can
contain my thoughts 140 characters but
so figuring out what it is I want to
write and just writing and so that's
what I'll be doing right after this
video is sitting down and writing for an
hour and then trying to meditate - too
many things going on every day to
meditate every day which my hundred days
of meditation is over but I'm never
stopping so but that's gonna be
continuing my hundred videos ends around
the end of the year and I'm doing it
after pre contemplate why it is that I'm
doing it but to get some amount of
YouTube following which is clearly not
work you don't think anyone see viewed
any one of my videos but because I want
I don't know how many people on YouTube
want like also want followers they want
to be famous on YouTube I don't like me
myself personally I could care less in
fact it's kind of scary for me that I
could be known when I'm walking out and
about in the world or
that just what comes with being YouTube
famous but I need to have people hear my
message so that I can get the right
people on board and just like I will
leave my comfort zone for my child I
will leave my comfort zone for this and
so I am actually quite comfortable
sharing vulnerable stuff with people
sharing it online is a whole other story
but that's why I'm doing these videos to
practice showing up exactly as I am and
not filtering or literary filtering
because I'm not in any way editing these
videos still and maybe I'll get through
a hundreth of editing all the other
reason was that I was gonna learn how to
edit videos and that hasn't felt like
the right time yet I'm still I still
figure to get this idea out into the
world which if I thought videos was the
way then I would learn how to edit them
but I can't do I can't explain in a five
minute video no matter how hard I try so
I'm going to explain it in a book
instead and so that's my focus for
explaining it and this is my it's just
another way it's something for me to do
and get out there and I'm almost a
quarter done I should have been a
quarter done today but like I said I
missed missed two of them so here's my
rambling for three and a half minutes
hope everybody has a great weekend I've
had my my hair fur for a week now today
I guess you gotta see with my broken
glasses and to get new glasses your new
glasses and you bed in a new car so I
need to be YouTube rich to make some
money but that sorry it's not really
accurate no plan to make you money off
of us but yeah hope everybody has a good
weekend and see you on Saturday because
I still need to do videos this again